http://www.cable-modem.net/privacy-policy/

Cable-modem.net is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy will provide information to you regarding how we collect and use your personal information, and about choices you have concerning our use of such information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. From time to time, we may revise this Privacy Policy to address new issues or changes to our practices. These changes will be posted here so that you will always know our privacy policies. Please check this Privacy Policy periodically to see if there have been any revisions.If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy practices, please send us an email at info@cable-modem.net or mail us at the following address:Cable-modem.net C/o Consumer Knowledge Network 2124 West Pratt Ave. #316 Chicago, IL 60645-4666
Scope of Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy applies to cable-modem.netâ€™s method of collection and use of information gathered by us for the customers that we serve on https://www.cable-modem.net (the “Web Site”). However, please note that the privacy practices of our service providers are not covered by this Privacy Policy. In addition, once you leave our Web Site via a link or otherwise, this Privacy Policy does not apply and cable-modem.net cannot and is not responsible for how data and information obtained from you on other Web sites is used by the operators of such Web sites.
Enforcement
Cable-modem.net monitors data center metrics on approximately a weekly basis. Network vulnerability testing and standard NOC monitoring are provided by the data center administration staff, with options for performing third-party security audits on demand.Cable-modem.net performs full recovery tests prior to live deployment of a new application or server system. Cable-modem.net performs recovery tests of backup media on a monthly to quarterly schedule to assure that existing backup regimes have created working recovery sets.Cable-modem.net actively monitors current and upcoming regulatory and compliance issues through outside legal resources.
Information Collected by cable-modem.net
Personal information (“Personal Information”) may include the following:
nameaddress (billing, shipping)email addressphone number(s)age (optional)
gender (optional)
We may request Personal Information from you in connection with your use of, or participation in, the Web Site, including applications, registrations, suggestions or requests for additional information, or in connection with other services or resources provided on or through the Web Site. Personal Information is collected on servers owned and maintained by a third party and leased to cable-modem.net exclusively. A confidentiality agreement exists between cable-modem.net and such third party.If, and only if, you indicated during the application or registration process you’d like to receive advertising and promotional materials related to cable-modem.net, we may also use your Personal Information to send information from our media partners or service providers. On occasion, for example, we or our media partners and service providers, may send you email to introduce products or services that might be of interest to you. We may also use your Personal Information to keep in touch with you when necessary, for example, to send to you confirmation, rebuttal, shipment or reminder email messages. If you identify yourself to us by sending us an email with questions or comments, we may use your Personal Information to respond to your questions or comments. (We may also file your comments for future reference.) We may also share Personal Information with our service providers and vendors. We will attempt to require that each of these service providers and vendors not use or disclose your Personal Information for any purpose other than providing you or us with products and services. However, we cannot guarantee their compliance with these restrictions. Cable-modem.net does not sell Personal Information to third parties.We reserve the right to provide or use your Personal Information in the following circumstances. We will release specific information about you or your account to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute or court order. We will also release specific information in special cases, such as if there is an attempted breach of the security of the Web Site, or a physical threat to you or others.
Passively Collected Information and the Use of Cookie Technology
To help make our site more responsive to the needs of our visitors, cable-modem.net may passively collect certain information without your prior consent. Such information (collected in standard Web server logs) may include your IP address, browser type, and Web access times. Such passively collected information is used in standard Web traffic analysis, in conjunction with demographic/aggregate analysis of collected user records.We may also collect information through the use of “cookies” which are small computer files that are transferred to a computer’s hard drive and which permit us to know about site visits. We may use cookies to improve your experience on the Web Site by making it easier for you to navigate through the Web Site or to make a Web Site feature work better. Information collected from a “cookie” might include information regarding your browser, type of computer, operating system, Internet service provider and other similar information. Cookie technology may also gather information about the areas you visit on our Web Site and about the links you may select from within our Web Site to other areas of the Internet. We can build a better Web Site if we know which pages our users are visiting and how often.We do not extract Personal Information during this process. Currently, only session cookies are used to maintain tracking of a user through an application. Session cookies expire at the end of a Web page visit. Session cookies contain only a numeric session identifier. We use such information in the aggregate to understand which services and resources our visitors prefer and how those services and resources are used.We may share aggregate demographic/statistical information with our media partners, service providers and other third parties. In addition, cable-modem.net may allow some of our advertisers to display ads which solicit or contain technology to collect information about users.Most browsers are set to accept cookies, however, you can set your browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, please note that some parts of the Web Site may not be accessible or function properly.
Privacy of Children
We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. Neither the cable-modem.net Web Site nor activities are intended for or designed to attract children under the age of 13. We do not collect Personal Information from any person we actually know is a child under the age of 13.
Links to Other Web Sites
Our Web Site contains links to other Web sites operated by third parties that may be of interest to you. However, we do not and cannot control the information and content or links contained on these sites. We do not and cannot control the way in which these Web sites collect and/or use your Personal Information. Therefore, cable-modem.net disclaims any liability for any third party’s use of your Personal Information obtained through using the third party Web site.
Access to Personal Information
Please note that certain information transmitted to cable-modem.net may not be later modified or retrieved by cable-modem.net. However, at your request, we will use reasonable efforts to provide you with access to your Personal Information (if we still retain it) and to revise, update or replace Personal Information that you inform us is in error. We cannot guarantee the actions of our service providers after we inform them of any changes.Certain Personal Information may be stored indefinitely so that cable-modem.net can access data for any customer service issue as well as report on aggregate data in the future.
